What is it now this early?
You're going to bury my livestock again?
No, Its just a normal inspection,
there's just a small leak at the site.
Go ahead, move along.
Why are you doing this to me?
Just like the last time?
I promise, not this time, now move along.
Go.
What a really bad day, rough morning,
what...
Come on.
Oh come on!
What a really rough day for me.
Madame,
statistical data companies we showed
abnormal in stock market.
Please do not liquidate your investment now.
The market will fall once
you've taken your investment...
Yes, I understand.
No, it is not.
I will do it as soon as possible.
Yes.
It will be run according to your wishes.
Please take care!
Come into my office.
What is the matter?
Sell all of our assets in the stock market.
Selling it all?
Yes.
Isn't it too risky to do that?
Still we could maintain our first asset.
And wait if something better...
Mr. Kim.
Yes.
Just do what I tell you to do.
We must be watchful of the
possibility that happen.
Okay.
Wait a minute Mr.Kim.
What's the popular gift for kids nowadays?
Forget it. You really can't be a good dad to Su-an.
You didn't even attend her recital.
I did not forget that.
There's a lot of work here.
She can stay here in Seoul with me.
Just send her here in Busan!
You've already broke your promises!
How many times have you told her that you'll come.
Can't you keep it just this once?
Yes I promise we all go.
You really don't keep your words.
I'm keeping my words...
You just have to keep your words.
Children are tired of always
with the promise…
Never mind, I'll talk to you...
You know that its her birthday tomorrow right?
I know!
Oh, you're here now.
Thank you...
Where is she?
She was playing in her room...
When will we see each other?
Why? Mom did not talk to dad huh?
I'm gonna hang the phone now, he's here.
It's okay you can talk to her.
I already hung-up.
Here.
You thought I forgot?
Happy birthday.
Well? Open it.
Why? You don't like it?
Last year on children's day too.
Well, tell me what you want.
Busan.
I want to go to mom at Busan.
Tomorrow...
Yeah, just wait.
We definitely go there after
father finished...
No.
Tomorrow.
Dad always say we'll go next time.
Anyway, tomorrow we have to go...
You don't have to come with me.
Grant my wish for once.
Is there a lot of work?
Yes there is.
Are you going to Busan tomorrow?
Yes.
You did good. Try talking with your
wife when you arrive there.
It's not good if you just break-up like that.
You two should re-unite again.
There is nothing wrong
you are together again...
Try it this time so that
you can come back again...
Mother...
I do not want to talk about it...
Let it be the past...
OK...
Do not be too busy with work...
Sometimes you should not always focus
on work. Su-an is growing up.
She also needs you.
Take care of your family, especially Su-an.
It's okay.
It's okay, continue singing...
Applause for Soo-an...
Yeah... ma...
No...
I'm with Dad.
Yeah, I'll see you there...
You thought father did not
know that you didn't finished the song.
How did you know?
You weren't there.
Father always know what you've been doing.
You got nervous right?
Am I right?
Yes.
Why did you do that? You'll look like
a fool if you don't finish it.
When you started something.
You should finish it no matter what.
You should know that…
Ah… that was close.
What's going on?
Su-an, are you okay?
You're surprised right?
It surprised me. It suddenly came out.
It looks like a big fire.
All departing passengers, kindly board the train now
as this train is now ready to depart for Busan.
Excuse me, where is the south station?
South station, you need to go that way...
-Kyo-shi! Kyo-shi!
- Yes?
Your scarf.
Please rest during this trip.
Good.
Wow, Jihee is here.
What do you mean, I'm coming with you.
I'm your cheerleader.
-How are you all ?
-Good...
Finally... also fresh eyes...
Finally...
Hey, go find another seat okay.
Stingy you did not want to share...
Hey, if your’re thankful to see me,
Just say "Thank you".
Even the "tools" you also right for you...
She's right...
Accept her. Accept her.
Here, eat this.
Aigoo...
Where did you get that egg.
Eat it yourself.
-Eat this.
-No, I don't like.
-Chief, Are you already on board?
-Yes, but why?
There are problems in the office...
let us take care of it.
Really?
We'll discuss it after I get back.
I'll be there after lunch.
-See you later...
-Good.
I'm so sorry… I’m so sorry...
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Are you the one in-charge?
-Yes.
I’ve seen a suspicious passenger.
-Where is the passenger?
-Inside the lavatory,
-It's been a while since then.
-Really? Lets see..
Ahh. I apologize sir.
I will check on it.
Passenger?
Everyone is dead.
Mister.
-I'm sorry, but may I see your ticket?
-Everyone is dead…
Mister, if you don't have a ticket
we need to drop you off on the next station.
Everyone is dead
Hey kid, if you don't study well,
you'll end up like him.
My mother told me not to say
those kinds of words.
Well, it looks like your mother didn't study well
Passengers please don't stay here
In a hurry?
We'll, you'll need to find another place
because it will take a while.
You could use the other comfort room.
Go there.
It will really take a while.
Baby? How are you doing down there?
Ahhh.. sorry, go ahead,
take your time... take your time...
Go there, go there...
She's gone, she's gone...
relax... relax...
Miss? Miss, are you okay?
Miss? What to do..
Chief!
-Hello?
-Yes, Kim?
It's more serious than we anticipated.
It's not just an overnight Ansan incident.
I don't know whats happening,
but it's not a simple strike.
Military Deployed to Control Riots
They say it's nationwide
-What about breathing?
-Hello?
But her seizure is uncontrollable!
Sir, what should we do?
I'll call you back.
Indiscriminate Violence at Riot
Oh no, they'll get hurt.
That's terrible.
People nowadays will riot over anything.
In the old days, they'd be re-educated.
You mustn't say that.
Look, look.
What's up with them?
Miss?
What do I do..
Chief? Chief where are you?
I don't believe this...
Chief?
Min Ji? Min Ji?
What is that? What is happening.
What is this?
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hurry! Everyone Run!
Stand up!
Conductor!
We have a situation here!
Run! Run!
-Oh my God!
-What in the hell!?
Get away! Just go!
Get out of here! Head for the back!
Get up! Hurry!
Daddy!
Baby?
Sang-hwa! So damn loud!
Sorry, the thing is...
Get off me!
You idiot! Go help her!
Hey!
What's with you?!
Have you gone mad?!
Baby?
Sung-Kyung!
You can run, right?
Get Away!
Close the door! The door!
Shut the door!
Quick!
Shut it!
Shut it now!
Just shut it!!!
I know her!
Where's the lock?
Buddy, how do I lock this?
Do you hear me?
Let it go.
What?
I don't think they know how to open.
They attack because they see us.
What in the...
What are they?
Su-an, you okay?
Hey buddy.
What is it?
Don't you owe me an apology?
What do you mean?
Look at this chump.
You shut the door in our faces, asshole!
You weren't the only ones in danger!
What a piece of work.
Come here.
I'll feed you to them.
Stop it!
Everyone's just scared.
Attention please!
Due to our current situation,
we wont be stopping in Cheonan,
For your safety, please stay in your seats.
Hello, anyone there?
Yes, go ahead.
Do you even know what's going on back here?
Why aren't you stopping at Cheonan?
We're aware, sir
This is the order from the control center.
Please be seated.
That's nonsense!
People are going rabid!
Stop in Cheonan, got it?!
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry but could she sit down?
She's pregnant.
Okay
Sit, sit.
Thank you.
Mom.
Are you on your way?
Yes, we're en route.
Where are you? Why is it so loud?
What's happening you say?
Everyone's fighting.
Are you and Su-an okay?
Why're you breathing like that, are you hurt?
Seok-woo, my baby.
Please take care of Su-an...
Mom, you okay?
My dear Su-an...
I love her so much, but she only wants her mom...
That bitch!
Mom?
Dad!
Is granny okay?
What the hell?
Sweetie, sit down.
My fellow citizens...
we're currently experiencing violent
riots in all major cities,
resulting in many civilian and police injuries.
Riots led to shutting down of various districts,
and the rioters have forcibly
attempted to destroy
or take government property.
For this reason,
we're entering state of emergency,
in order to control current situations.
Thanks to our government's rapid response,
various outbreaks are being contained.
Fellow citizens, please refrain from
reacting to baseless rumors,
and stay in the safety of your homes.
We must stay calm and trust the government,
in order to overcome such trying obstacle.
We believe that your safety is not in jeopardy.
Analyst Kim
Mommy's phone is off.
Those in the front, hurry up!
Su-an, sit over here.
Don't worry, i'll give her a call.
Jong-gil, come sit down.
-You're older, you sit down.
-I'm fine, take it.
Baby, let's go over there.
Ma'am, take my seat.
-I'm okay.
-No, please sit.
Child, would you like one?
-Thank you!
-What a great kid.
-We both got seats.
-Keep walking.
Su-an, you didn't have to do that.
-Do what?
-Being good.
At a time like this,
only watch out for yourself.
Answer me.
Granny always had knee aches.
Sweetie...
May I have you attention please, our train
will conclude service at Daejeon station.
Military is deployed there,
and will secure our train,
so once we arrive, please exit the train.
I repeat, DAEJEON STATION is our last stop.
Which cities can be entered?
Yeosu, Uljin, Busan.
What about Daejeon?
Excuse me, I need to use it.
Why not?!
Sweetie, stay put.
Hey, kiddo.
Yes?
Who is he? Your dad?
Yes.
-Real dad?
-Yes.
I wanna know.
What does he do?
He's a fund manager.
-Fund manager?
-Yes
He's a bloodsucker.
He leaches off others.
Don't say that in front of his child.
It's okay.
That's what everyone thinks.
Want some?
It's what Sleepy eats.
This is Sleepy. Say hello.
Baby's name is Sleepy?
No, the foetus name.
It's like a nickname,
he's daddy too lazy
to come up with a name yet.
Touch her belly.
Right here.
Go on.
Felt it?
I made that.
-You idiot...
-But it's true, No?
-Mr. Suh, you called me at a bad time...
-Wait, Wait!
Let me ask you something,
What?
I'm on KTX to Daejeon.
KTX? Right this minute?
Yes, I'm almost there,
Is it true military is deployed in Daejeon?
Yes, that's correct.
Is that so? It must be safe there.
Well... it's...
Min, it is safe, right?
Once you arrive, you'll be quarantined.
What?
I'm with my daughter.
Can you help me and my daughter?
But the thing is...
I'll get you a real scoop, do me a favor.
Don't go to the main square,
come to the East one.
I'll let my men know.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks so much.
All dead... all dead...
What's going on?
So quiet.
Is it Daejeon?
There's nobody.
Why isn't anyone here?
What's going on back there?
This is that violent incident I told you about.
-You’re the conductor?
-Yes.
How many can fit in the engine car?
We must uncouple it and go to Busan.
-Uncouple?
-Yes!
-We can't!
-Why not?!
It can't be done here.
Then, where's the military?
Right...
I only received a report about it...
Where's my business card...
I'm COO of Stallion Express,
all routes into Daejeon are cut off.
Our busses are all rerouted.
But what for?
The city's been quarantined!
They probably won't let us in.
But Busan is still open, let's go there!
Wait, if that's true...
-We just take others.
-Take who?!
Let's check the station first.
Hey!
Dammit!
Don't mind them.
-Come on sweetie.
-Where are we going?
We're going this way.
-Just us?
-Yes, let's go.
What is it?
I'm going this way too.
Main square is that way,
just follow other people.
I'm gonna come with you.
I heard your phone call.
About pulling you two out.
I know others will be quarantined.
It's not true, Su-an.
I'll go tell the others.
-You don't have to.
-Of course I do!
Forget them!
We're all on our own!
You only care about yourself.
That's why mommy left.
Sweetie...
Here! Over here!
Please help!
Sweetie, stay right here.
Goddamit!
Hold on!
Go back up! Go! Go!
Mr. Min.
-Mr. Suh!
-Is everything okay there?
I can't contact my men!
Hello?
Help me...
Come on! Hurry!
Hurry up! Quick!
Take this!
Run! Come on!
Asshole! Come on!
Faster!
Hold them off!
-Over here! Run!
-This way! Hurry!
Here!
This way!
Come on!
Hurry!
Why aren't we leaving yet?!
There are still more people!
Hurry up!
Come this way!
Hurry!
Faster! Here!
Granny!
Please get up!
No, stop!
My sister!
Hop on!
Me too!
Let me in!
Please!
How much longer?
We have to leave!
No! My friends aren't here yet!
Those onboard must survive!
Ain't I right?
Conductor.
Please... depart.
Run! Let's go!
Look, the train!
Run faster!
Snap out of it, idiot!
Watch out!
Control, 101 could not dock
at Daejeon due to outbreak.
Advise which station is available to dock, over.
101, due to unstable comm,
it is difficult to advise.
Control, is 101 clear to reach Busan?
Over.
101, we'll clear your route to Busan.
Control center, out.
Advise when you make contact with Busan.
101, out.
Attention everyone.
For those safety of those on board,
we won't be making any stops,
and head straight for Busan.
Conductor, can you hear me?
Go ahead.
Were you able to contact Busan?
No, the communication is erratic.
Full speed, no matter what!
Or we won't get in, understand?
Youngguk, where are you?
I thought you were dead!
I'm sorry!
No one else made it!
I'm sorry.
-Baby?
-Mister!
Huh? Why are you answering?
Where are you?
We're in the train washroom!
Washroom? Which car?
Well... it's...
Car 13!
-Get your ass over here!
-Baby
Was that my kid?
Is she okay?
Washroom in car 13.
Gonna pass through?
Let's say you got through and rescue them,
how will you come back?
In car 15,
People are gathered there.
Only 4 cars away.
I'll lead...
you in the middle...
and you in the back.
Block anyone attacking from the rear.
I heard you're a fund manager.
Then you're an expert...
at leaving useless people behind.
Wait till we exit the tunnel.
Let's go.
Come on!
Let's go!
Move.
Out of the way.
They stopped once we
entered the tunnel, right?
Probably because of darkness.
Yeah, I think so too.
There are even more here.
What do we do now?
There's no way around it.
Let's go.
Get that out of my face.
Yo, douche.
Felt good to see your kid, thanks to me?
Are you grateful or what?
Why is your ringtone so tacky?
What's wrong with it?
How do I change it?
Am I funny? You little rat?
How tall are you?
181 cm.
10 km away, at 300 km/h...
What?
2 minutes, upcoming tunnel will give us 2 minutes.
-Can we do it?
-We gotta.
If we miss this one,
there's another in 3 km...
I bet you never get to
play with your daughter.
When she gets older,
she'll understand why you work so hard.
Dads get all the bad rap and no praise,
but it's all about sacrifice, right?
What's with the look?
Did I sound cool?
People rescued. Heading over now.
My friend's coming here!
What did you say?
My friend from another car is coming over.
-Who's coming?
-My friend!
He was in car 9, and he rescued some people.
Rescued?
From there to here,
passing through those monsters?
Without any injuries?
You sure they're not infected?
Are you damn sure?!
What do you mean?
Look, look at them.
At a moment like this,
no one knows what happened to their families.
We don't even know if your
damn friends are infected!
But allow them in here?!
I don't believe this.
Sir...
Please say something.
They'll be here soon.
Sir!
Get over here.
One!
Two!
Run!
Jin-hee! Jin-hee!
Hurry the hell up!
Open up!
Hey! Open this door!
Jin-hee!
Open this door!
-Open up!
-Jin-hee! Jin-hee!
Open it now!
It wont budge!
It can't open it!
Smash it!
Stand back!
Hurry up!
You stupid idiots!
Come on!
In-gil!
Young-guk!
Stand back!
Stay away!
Stay back, baby. Please go!
Buddy, hey!
Take her and leave.
You have to go!
I said go, douche!
I'm getting tired, please go.
Take care of her, okay?
I'll hold them off, just go!
I'm sorry...
We have to go, let's go!
Yoon Su-yun!
Our baby's name!
Got it?
Why did you do it?!
You bastard!
We could've save them!
Why?!
He's infected!
He's one of them!
This guy's infected!
His eyes! Look at his eyes!
He'll become one of them!
Do you all want to die?!
We must throw them out!
Those of you who just arrived,
I don't think you can stay with us.
Please move to the vestibule.
Just go!
Get out!
Get out now!
Hurry up!
Move!
Go!
Leave us!
Get the hell out!
Out now!
Hurry!
It'll be safer for you to stay here.
No, I don't want to stay.
I'm coming with you.
But...
Get the hell out!
What are you waiting for!
Okay, let's go.
Get out! Rest of you!
Get out!
Get out of here!
Let's go.
Tie it faster!
More ties! Neckties!
Shut up! I'm working on it!
Yun In-gil
Great name.
Always helping others instead of yourself.
Why did you live like that?
What was the point?
So stupid...
Shut up! Be quiet!
Stay in your seat!
What a load of shit.
Finish up and do the other side too.
Thank you for everything.
That woman...
Stop her!
Control, this is Busan-bound 101!
Requesting current situation in Busan, over.
Control!
It's your birthday...
Don't worry.
I'll take you to mom no matter what.
Aren't you scared?
Of course I am.
I'm scared too.
I was so scared.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I practiced that song just for you.
That's why I couldn't sing.
Because I didn't see you.
Will you stay with me?
Ex-wife
The person you're calling is not available...
Analyst Kim
Yes, Kim.
Have you arrived in Busan?
Not yet, where are you?
Is it okay there?
Busan succeeded in initial defense.
What?
You sure?
Where did you hear this from?
Chief, we are the one who started this.
Our plant started all of this.
Chief, please tell me it's not our fault.
We're only doing our jobs right?
Is this my fault?
It's...
It's not your fault.
Thank you...
Kim...
Attention please.
Due to a blockage on our track,
we have stopped at East Daegu Station.
We should either wait for the rescue team,
or we'll have to reach Busan in another train.
As soon as I end this announcement,
I will find a working train
and put it on left most track.
-What's going on?
-I repeat, left most track.
If you're alive, please transfer safely.
Godspeed.
Will there be a rescue?
I heard that Busan is safe.
We have to move now.
Coast clear?
Yeah.
You go ahead.
We've got to find a way across.
What in the...
Over here!
No...
Oh no...
What now...
We have to move, come on!
Jin-hee, let's go!
Stand back!
Jin-hee!
This can't be...
I'm sorry...
Daddy! Wake up!
Daddy! Daddy!
What's going on?
Come on faster! Faster!
Dammit!
Help!
Sweetie, come here!
Su-an, Su-an!
Mister!
Sweetie!
Su-an, come here!
Mister...
Go! Hurry!
Come on!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry!
Daddy!
Mister.
Please bring me to Busan.
Please help me.
My mother is waiting for me.
Please bring me home…
Please save me.
You are already infected.
No, no, no, no...
Su-an come here. Sit here.
Listen to me...
Here is the throttle, the brakes.
When you need to stop, pull the breaks.
Su-an.
Look at me...
Su-an...
Listen to me.
You must stay with her, okay?
Busan is still safe, that is why...
that is why...
Don't go!
Don't go father!
Come with us.
Please don't leave me...
Don't go...
You should come with us.
Please come with us.
Don't go...
Father! Father!
Father!
No! Don't go!
I see something.
2 subjects approaching at our location.
Looks like a woman and a child.
Are you able to verify the subjects?
It's so dark on the other side.
I can't clearly see them.
Can't clearly see the subjects, unable to verify.
Kill them.
2 survivors approaching.